notefull.com 2014-03-31

# NOTEFULL

Great news: We've designed a new "How To Choose Your Program Page" to make the process of registering for the right program even easier. _**[Please click here to check it out!](https://www.notefull.com/content.php?pgID=251)**_

### Privacy Policy

You're privacy is very important to us. We want to make sure that you have a great, positive experience at NoteFull. Below you'll find information that is relevant to how we use your information to better help you succeed.

To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

1) Collection of Personal Information

When visiting this website, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track the movement of users and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

2) Links to Third-party Websites

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

3) Third-party Advertising

Third party vendors, including Google, may show you ads on other sites on the Internet relating to our website.  Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to this website.Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

4) Changes to this Privacy Statement

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of this website then you may contact us using the contact form on this website.  
  
---  
  
### COMMENTS

* * *

4 entries 

* * *

| 

Reply

najat wrote on Sunday March 30, 2014 12:12pm   
Hey, I lost my password and I forgot the zip code that I wrote .And I aant tonight to buy the coyrse but I can not enter to.my account .Please help me because I want to get discount for early bird . Thanks my e-mail najat_2005@yahoo.com   
---  
  
* * *  
  
Reply

Madhu Vanga wrote on Saturday February 1, 2014 5:17pm   
hey i am Madhu vanga , i registered with you on dec 31st and i took my toefl on june 17th 2014 my scores are R-24, L-22, S-24 AND W-22 . I am taking once again toefl on feb 8th so please help me out for crossing that dpeaking and writing to 26 and 24 for my pharmacy license. please help me out please.   
  
* * *  
  
Reply

LeahFromNoteFull wrote on Tuesday July 30, 2013 11:08am 

**DAN SU said**  
" _Can I return my vocabulary course? Because I don't like to learn word in that way, maybe it more difficult for me to learn in English. And I bought this e-book just now._ "

Hello Dan, Thanks for posting. We completely understand your situation and will review it carefully. Please send an email with your request, including your first and last name and the email address on your account, to StudentHelp@NoteFull.com. We look forward to helping you.   
  
* * *  
  
Reply

DAN SU wrote on Sunday July 28, 2013 6:23pm   
Can I return my vocabulary course? Because I don't like to learn word in that way, maybe it more difficult for me to learn in English. And I bought this e-book just now.   
  
* * *
